# TRI KHUONG QUAN

**BACK FND** 



### **Profile**

Returning from Japan after two years learning abroad, I am currently dedicated to a new found passion of game development, and honing my skill as a developer. Outside of school, I'm also spend my time to do multiple project that give me the change to use multiple programming languages like: Java, C++, C# and python.

#### Education

2017 - 2019 Tokyo World Japanese Language School

Language School, Tokyo

A good experience to learn about the culture

of Japan.

2021 - 2024 Greenwich University

University, Ho Chi Minh

Currently learning and experiencing

international working culture from Greenwich.

# Experience

2017 - 2019 Izakaya restaurant

Part-timer, Tokyo

Tried out all of the position, from main chief

to dish washer.

2021 - 2024 Greenwich university

Student, Ho Chi Minh city

Experience multiple realistic project from front end static web, to back end dynamic web, including handling platform and

database.

#### Skills

Can use multiple OOP

- languages: Java, C++, C#, python.
- Can use English and Japanese
- ✓ Team work
- ✓ Work under pressure
- Communication
- **✓** Time management

#### Contact

- A Binh Tan, Ho Chi Minh
- 0332565790
- in www.linkedin.com/in/trikhuong-quan-b5260416b
- https://github.com/Tristory? tab=repositories

# Additional activities

- Working as volunteer in a distribute event.
- Running a personal RPG project using unity.

# **Career Objective**

**Short**: Gaining experience as a developer. In both aspects of soft skill and hard skill. Explore how to make product in more professional way.

Long: Gaming has long been an underrated field, their application Gaming has long been an underrated field, their application has never been too far from the entertainment industry, which is a huge waste of potential. Time and time again, multiple research papers have come out to prove the undeniable stimulus effect of gaming, which demands minimal physical effect. I want to explore such possibilities and push them further.

## Certificate

#### **IELTS(2021)**



6.5 overall, and 8.0 for reading



JLPT(2018)